Solve to survive.
No Escape Room is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Alex Merkin.
A father and daughter check out a small town escape room and
discover there is something sinister about the place.
Karen, played by Jeni Ross.
Michael, played by Mark Ghanimé.
Tyler, played by Hamza Haq.
Melanie, played by Kathryn Davis.
Andrew, played by Dennis Andres.
Josie, played by Brianna Barnes.
Escape Room is a 2018 American horror film directed by
Peter Dukes and starring Skeet Ulrich.
The film centers on a group of survivors who
challenged themselves to an escape room.
The owner of the place bought an antique demonic box to be used as a prop, which turns
out to be evil that possesses whoever opens it and kills the victims.
The film explores themes of key, haunting, diner, ghost, locked door.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.